tigernt.com 2015-04-07

# Privacy Statement

##  Privacy Statement for TigerNT 

**TigerNT** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ TigerNT ](http://www.tigernt.com/)

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. __

####  Cookies 

Our Site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. _We use cookies to store user preference selection, such as output encoding, word lookup history, etc.)_

####  Advertisers 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

####  Registration Forms 

The registration form in Good Deal Hunting page requires users to give us email address information. 

Email address from the registration forms is used to send promotional material from us to our users. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **TigerNT** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Public Forums 

This site may makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

####  Choice/Opt-Out 

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us . 

  1. You can visit the following URL: [ http://www.tigernt.com/deals/remove.cgi ](http://www.tigernt.com/deals/remove.cgi)

##  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Support
